{
    "id": "6f1d299432d4498f8b6607cc3b8f6b59",
    "title": "Advanced level grammar review: exercise 2",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8242fd7ae814459ca5058afd4d8e9fe7",
            "title": "Grammar Review Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If I ……………………… about your problems, I would have helped you.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "know",
                        "knew",
                        "had known"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has agreed to ……………………….. my dogs while I am away on holiday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "look at",
                        "look for",
                        "look after"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "They made the child ………………………. the milk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "drink",
                        "to drink",
                        "drinking"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She makes her children ……………………………… their lessons everyday.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "learn",
                        "to learn",
                        "learning"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The test was …………………… .. difficult that she couldn’t answer many questions.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "too",
                        "so",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I …………………….. this work by next week.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "would finish",
                        "will finish",
                        "will have finished"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She ……………………… by the time we arrived.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "left",
                        "has left",
                        "had left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "When I stopped …………………….. to him, he was working in his garden.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "speaking",
                        "to speak",
                        "speak"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Despite ……………………. hard, he failed the exam.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "work",
                        "to work",
                        "working"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He ………………….. play a lot of tennis when he was young.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "used to",
                        "was to",
                        "will"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}